Alfred H. Barr, Jr. Papers
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - College Art Association &Art Journal, Brown, Richard F. Coffin, David R. (The Art Bulletin, Princeton University; incl. 4 TLS) Costable, W. G. (Museum of Fine Arts, Boston) Deknatel, Frederick B. (Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University) Dodd, Lamar Elsen, Albert Faison, S. Lane, Jr. (University of Georgia) Goodrich, Lloyd (Whitney Museum of American Art; letter to the editor) Hayes, Bartlett H. Hope, Henry (Indiana University; incl. 4 ALS, 4 TLS, AHB TLS) Meiss, Millard (The Institute for Advanced Study; incl. TLS) Messer, Thomas M. (The American Federation of Arts) Parkhurst, Charles (incl. TLS) Robb, David M. (University of Pennsylvania) Schmeckebier, Laurence (Cleveland Institute of Art; incl. 2 TLS) Wellemeyer, J. F. (American Council of Learned Societies) File incl. preliminary program of 1957 January 24-27 annual meeting and 1966 January 27-29 anuual meeting of CAA, checklist of foreign paperback, AHB handwritten notes, minutes of 1958 January 30 meeting of the Art Bulletin, AHB letter to the editor, 1956 Spring and 1955 Fall issue of College Art Journal (Box 1, Folder 1.430 mf 2192:904)
  - Columbia University, 1960-1974; Barzun, Jacques (incl. article Centering the Arts, 3 TLS) Cordier, Andrew W. Collins, George R. (incl. corresp. re.Modern Architecture Symposium 1964) Davis, Howard McP. Erpf, Armand G. Faunce, Sarah (incl. memo re: expansion of the photograph collection) Frese, Walter (Hastings House, Publishers, Inc.) Grimm, Peter Hastings, John Hitchcock, Henry-Russell (statement The Decade 1929-1939) Kirk, Grayson (incl. progress report on Oil Sketch Exhibition, report on the Exhibition Committee for the Czanne Watercolor Show, report of the Committee on Exhibitions and Public Relations) McGill, William J. Nelson, Clifford C. Placzek, Adolf K. (incl. proceedings in the Modern Architecture Symposium) Remond, Roland Sevcenko, Mrs., Ihor Taylor, Davisdon Vogel, Edwin C. (incl. report of the Advisory Council chairman to the Columbia University President 1967 October) Walsh, Mrs., Lawrence E. Whiteside, W. J. Wittkower, Rudolf File incl.: Agenda for Advisory Council Meetings: 1972 November 16 1971 October 1970 December 9 1970 April 28 1969 April 9 Minutes of Advisory Council Meetings 1972 May 12 1971 October 21 1969 December 4 1969 April 9 1968 April 3 1967 October 24 1966 December 1 1966 May 4 1965 November 16 1965 April 28 1964 April 21 1963 May 13 1963 January 22 1962 November 7 1962 April 9 1962 January 17 Annual Report of the Department of Art History and Archeology: 1962 July 1961 June 1960 June Press release Proposed amendments to by-laws of Advisory Council to Department of Art History and Archeology List of standing committees and current projects Membership list of the Advisory Council and Executive Committee, Bi-Annual report 1965-1966 Resums of Faculty Talks Report of the Committee of Development By-laws of the Advisory Council 1969 April 9 ad hoc committee report Minutes of the Executive Committee for Czanne exhibition 1963 January 22 Annual report of the Advisory Council of the Department of Art and Archeology 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1.431 mf 2192:2193)
  - Copley Foundation, 1954-1961, 1970-1972; Augustinci, R. A. (Galerie Rive Gauche) Cohen, George (incl. ALS) Copley, William N. M/M (incl. ALS) Day, Lucien (Green Mountain Gallery; incl. TLS) DeMott, Helen (incl. 3 ALS) Duchamp, Marcel (incl. 2 ALS) Echaurren, Matta (incl. ALS) File incl. clippings, press releases, 5 slides (Box 1, Folder 1.432 mf 2193:52)
  - Cooper [Douglas] / Penguin, 1952-1963, 1971; Cogswell, Margaret (The American Federation of Arts) Frost, Eunice (Penquin Books, Ltd.) Karpel, Bernard Ludington, Wright (The Santa Barbara Museum) Nicolson, Nigel (George Weidenfeld & Nicolson Ltd.) Orwell, Sonia (George Weidenfeld & Nicolson ltd.) Thompson, G. David File incl. clippings, ALS AHB-Cooper, 15 ALS Cooper, 11 TLS Cooper, AHB drafts of letter to the editor (Box 1, Folder 1.433 mf 2193:150)
  - Cordoba Show - Correspondence (general), 1966; Bulgheroni, Raul R. Burdman, Eleonora Crowder, Orville Gunther, John Kalenberg, Angel (Instituto General Electric) McCloud, J. F. Masjuan, Francisco (TLS) Martin, Edwin M. Soby, James Thrall Sörenson, Christian (Bienal Americana de Arte) Parkinson, Bliss E. Weintraub, William M. File incl. draft of AHB letter to McCloud (Box 1, Folder 1.434 mf 2193:308)
  - 1966, Ordnez, Mrs., Manuel Sörenson, Christian File incl. annotated list of participants in Bienal Americana de Arte (Box 1, Folder 1.435 mf 2193:383)
  - Cordoba: South American Artists, 1966; File incl. List of Argentines Painters, list of Latin American works acquired since 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1.436 mf 2193:398)
  - 1966, Becker, John File incl. 19 slides (Box 1, Folder 1.437 mf 2193:409)
  - Cordoba: Miscellaneous, 1966; Kert, Lewis (Department of State; ALS) McCloud, James F. Portinno, Carmen Velasco (Council on Leaders and Specialists; c.v.) Sörenson, Christian (TLS) Straus, Mrs., Donald B. Whitelow, Guillermo (Galeria Bonino; ALS) File incl. press release (Box 1, Folder 1.438 mf 2193:420)
  - Cordoba: Press, 1966; File incl. clippings (Box 1, Folder 1.440 mf 2193:515)
  - Critics, 1962; File incl.A Critic on the Side of History: Notes on Clement Greenberg by Hilton Kramer from 1962 October Arts Magazine (Box 1, Folder 1.441 mf 2193: [599])
  - D, 1966-1974; Day, Lucien (incl. 2 ALS) DeMott, Helen Dillenger, Mrs., John Delaunay, Sonia (incl. TLS) Delson, Theodore U. Devi, Mrs., P. Sarojini (Rachana) Dillon, Ripley (Smithsonian Institution) Doesburg, Mrs., Theo van Dorner, Lydia (incl. TLS) Drew, Jane B. Driscoll, Margaret Weyerhaeuser Duchamp, Marcel (corresp. re.) Duncan, Davis Douglas Duster, Troy (University of California) (Box 1, Folder 1.442 mf 2193:605)
  - Dada/Surrealism... (Rubin) [Bill], 1966; Rubin, William S. File incl. draft of Dada, Surrealism and Their Heritage by William Rubin 1966 July (Box 1, Folder 1.443 mf 2193:648)
  - Marcel Duchamp, 1968, 1973-1974; Gray, Cleve (incl. TLS) Limpert, Jr., John (list of Museum "winter weekend" activities) File incl. clippings, list of lectures during Marcel Duchamp exhibition (Box 1, Folder 1.444 mf 2193:661)
  - E, 1966-1973; Eagle, Joanne Shaw Ede, H. S. (University of Cambridge, England) Egbert, Donald Drew (Princeton University) Eisler, Colin Encyclopedia Britannica(Cohn, Leslie) Evans, Walker (incl. ALS) Ervin, Albert File incl. clippings (Box 1, Folder 1.445 mf 2193:687)
  - E.A.T. (Experiments in Art and Technology., Inc.), 1960-1970; Berkenmeier, Barbara Dorner, Lydia Hightower, John B. Klüver, J. Wilhelm Langsam, Edwin S. (American Telephone and Telegraph Company) Powers, John File incl. clippings, report on E. A. T. By W. Howard Adams,E. A. T. News 1968 March 18, 1967 June 1 (Box 1, Folder 1.446 mf 2193:707)
  - Esso Jury, 1965-1968; Clay, Vera Easther Stuttman Gallery Kingsley, Robert E. (International Petroleum Company; incl. 2 TLS) Morgan, Paul (Standard Oil Company) Watson, Ray File incl. press releases (Box 1, Folder 1.447 mf 2193:804)
  - Exhibition Proposals, 1960-1966; Arnason, Harvey H. (The Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum) Cantor, Joseph Cassou, Jean Elsen, Albert (Indiana University; incl. TL Elsen-President Johnson re: proposal on Fine Arts) Finn, David (Ruder & Finn Inc., TLS) Fischer, H. R. (Marlborough Fine Art Ltd., TLS) Hamilton, George Heard (Yale University) Schöffer, Nicholas Selz, Peter File incl. 1962 October-1963 November Exhibition schedule, minutes of program committee September 13 (Box 1, Folder 1.448 mf 2193:830)
  - Expo: 1967] Montreal, Besner, J. J. (The Art Gallery) Dupuey, Pierre (The Universal and International Exhibition of 1967, TLS) Lamothe, H. Lytle, Dorothy, L. (The Museum of Primitive Art) Marsden, Jeanne (The Art Gallery) Stern, Max (Dominion Gallery, TLS) Vance, David (ALS) (Box 1, Folder 1.449 mf 2193:869)
  - F, 1966-1970; Feigen, Richard (Richard Feigen Gallery) Ferber, Cornelia V. H. (Vassar College) Fera, Mary (corresp. re.) Finkler, Mrs., Joseph Finsthwait, Mrs., Robert A. (ALS) Fleming, Francesca Fort Worth Gardens (Johnson III, Mrs., Lee) Franklin, Danny (ALS) Fourcade, Xavier (M. Knoedler & Co., Inc.) Frazen, M/M Freed, Mrs., Frank Freedberg, Mrs., Sydney J. Frosso Ephtimisde Menegakis (MSB) Fry, Mrs., Varian File incl. clippings (Box 1, Folder 1.450 mf 2193:903)
  - Fakes/Fraud, 1956-1966; 1956-59, 1961, 1965-1966 Class, Peter (corresp. re: fake Henri Matisse) Easby, Jr., Dudley T. Emil, Allan D. Estorick, Eric Feigel, Marie-Suzanne (corresp. re: fake Modigliani) Koch, Richard A. (memo re: Discussion on the French Law of Art 1966 February 25) Lefkowitz, Louis J. File incl. clippings, b/w photograph (Box 1, Folder 1.451 mf 2193:942)
  - Fantastic Art/Dada, 1949-1971; 1949, 1954-1956, 1964, 1971 G. & C. Merriam Company (Gladstone, M. J.; corresp. re: Surrealism) Hulbeck, Charles R. Orengo, Charles (Librairie Plon) Pasto, Tarmo A. (Sacramento State College) psychopathic patients Rudenstine, Angelica File incl. clippings, b/w photograph (Box 1, Folder 1.452 mf 2193:974)
  - Family of Man, Society, 1966-1967; Ball, George W. (corresp. re: (Family of Man Awards Dinner 1967) Barr, Jr., Alfred Hamilton (TLS; incl. Notes on the candidacy of Edward Steichen for the Family of Man Award in the Arts) Bingham, Wheelock H. Fiorillo, Joaquin Gallagher, Buell G. (The City College, New York) Haider, Michael (progress report on Family of Man Awards Dinner 1966) Mayer, Grace (incl. ALS) Meyer, Mrs., Eugene Schoenbrun, David (Columbia University) Steichen, Edward File incl. supplementary list of candidates: science, world peace, communications, arts, education, human relations (Box 1, Folder 1.453 mf 2193:1009)
  - Franc, Helen, 1966; File incl. 2 memos Franc-AHB, TL Franc-AHB (Box 1, Folder 1.454 mf 2193:1169)
  - G, Gabetti, Gianluigi M/M (Olivetti Corporation of America; incl. ALS) Gee, Helen Geary, Mary de Forest Geldzahler, Henry (MMA) Gerlöti, E. (incl. 2 ALS) Glatman, David (corresp. re.) Gimbel, Mrs., Bernard F. Glimcher, Arnold (memo re.) Goldman Gordon, Donald (Dickenson College) Graham, F. Lanier (The Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco) Gregg, Lois H. (State University of New York at Albany) Gris, Romera Grohmann, Mrs., William Gropius, Walter Graubard, Stephen R. (Harvard University;Daedalus) Gunther, John Gustin, Philip (corresp. re.) Guzdek, Jerry (incl. ALS) File incl. clippings (Box 1, Folder 1.455 mf 2193:1174)
  - Gerstenzang, Ziuta [Mrs. Leo], 1962-1964; Akston, Joseph J. Burroughs, Josanne Larkin, Nina Nivel, Edith (Gallery 63) Primoff, Morris W. (Primoff & Primoff) Primoff, Robert L. Soby, James Thrall (incl. 2 TLS) Vass, Joan File incl. clippings, Gerstenzang ALS (Box 1, Folder 1.456 mf 2193:1237)
  - Van Gogh, Cummings, Burton (New York Graphic Society) Franco, Johan (incl. ALS) Harmacher, A. M. M. J. (Rijksmuseum) Lasker, Albert D. Leggett, John (Houghton Mifflin Company) Mettschen, Mr. Rich, Daniel Catton (Art Institute of Chicago) Rockefeller, Mrs., Laurance S. Van Gogh, V. W. (incl. 3 TLS, 2 ALS) File incl. press release (Box 1, Folder 1.457 mf 2193: [1303])
  - Gmez - Sicre [Jos], File mostly incl. AHB-Gmez and Gmez-AHB correspondence Barry, Veronica (Time) Gold, Berta (Time) Guenther, Peter W. (University of Houston) Peters, De Witt (Le Centre d'Art) Richards, Monawee A. File incl. clippings (Box 1, Folder 1.458 mf 2193:1365 mf 2194:6)
  - Goodyear [A. Conger], 1942; Smith, Gordon M. (Albright-Knox Gallery; incl. corresp. re: The Buffalo Fine Art Academy Goodyear fund) Soby, James Thrall File incl. clippings, press release, AHB handwritten draft of Goodyear letter (Box 1, Folder 1.459 mf 2194:50)
  - Camilla Gray, 1957-1972; Attis, Ben (Moderage Custom Darkrooms, Inc.) [Frampton], Kenneth (ALS) Gray, Basil (incl. ALS, TLS) Hess, Thomas B. Leverhulme Research Awards Lowman, Patricia Lowry, Bates Moeller, Pearl L. Spencer, Herbert (Typographica) File incl. clippings, 13 Gray ALS (Box 1, Folder 1.460 mf 2194:104)
  - Peggy Guggenheim, Barozzi, Paolo (incl. TLS) Charter, Margarette Colin, Ralph F. (2 TLS) Falkenstein, Claire Licht, Frederick (The Florida State University Study Center in Florence; TLS) O' Connor, Francis (incl. 2 ALS, TLS) Reis, Bernard J. (incl. TLS) File incl. clippings, Peggy Guggenheim 5 ALS, 7 TLS, 6 TLS with handwritten notes, 5 b/w photograph, AHB handwritten draft letter, AHB preface to Una Collezionista Ricorda by Peggy Guggenhiem, AHB notes to La Collezione Guggenheim (Box 1, Folder 1.461 mf 2194:226)
  - Mrs. Simon Guggenheim, 1939-1970; 1938, 1944, 1948-1949, 1950-1952, 1954-1959, 1961-1967, 1970 picture book: 1959] Bach, Otto Karl (The Denver Art Museum) Burden, William A. M. Case, White (White & Case; incl. TL Case-MoMA re: Guggenheim will) Lundell, Jr., Ernest M. (John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation; incl. TL; Richard H. Koch-Lundell re: memorial) Meiss, Millard (Institute for Advanced Studies) Miller, Dorothy Moe, Henry Allen (John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation; TLS) Pittman, Hobson Rockefeller, Nelson A. Russell, Haide (Consulate General of the Federal Republic of Germany) Soby, James Thrall (incl. TLS with handwritten notes) File incl. clippings, press releases, AHB handwritten notes, AHB TLS, 14 Guggenheim ALS, 2 b/w photographs, notes on Mrs. Guggenheim read by AHB at 1970 March 12 meeting of the Board of Trustees, (Box 1, Folder 1.462 mf 2194:402)
  - Guggenheim monographs, 1967-1968; Lieberman, Willam S. Seitz, William (Rose Art Museum, Brandeis University) Soby, James Thrall (5 TLS, Edward Hopper article with AHB corrections) Williams, Jr., Gray (incl. TLS) File incl. prints by Edward Hopper in the collection of MoMA, list of Mrs. Simon Guggenheim fund purchases (Box 1, Folder 1.463 mf 2194:648)
  - H, 1961, 1967-1973; Haacke, Hans Haag, Susanne (incl. 2 TLS) Haas, David Mathew (TLS) Haftmann, Werner (Staatlliche Museen, Berlin, incl. ALS) Haletsky, John T. (Sterling and Francine Clark Institute; incl. TLS) Halford, Lucy (Tandy Halford & Mills Limited) Harris, Jessica (incl. ALS) Harris, Stephen L. (Champlain College) Hartmann, William E. Hazen, Joseph H. Heckscher, August Hendricks, Gordon (incl. 2 ALS) Herbert, Robert L. (Yale University) Herzongenrath, Wulf Hess, Thomas B. (Art News) Hillman, Alex M/M (incl. ALS) Hirshhorn, Joseph H. M/M Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden (Garson, Inez; ALS; Lerner, Abram; TLS) Hiss, Philip (corresp. re.) Hitchcock, Henry-Russell Hichman, Elaine Hofmann, Werner Hole Fine Arts Foundation Holland, Kenneth (Institute for International Education) Holtman, Alice Honeyman, T. J. (University of Glasgow) Horwitt, Nathan George Houston (Adler, Sebastian; Contemporary Arts Museum) Howe, Letitia (corresp. re.) Hunt, Richard B. (Burns & Hunt) Huyghe, Ren (National Gallery of Art; incl. ALS) File incl. clippings, b/w photograph (Box 1, Folder 1.464 mf 2194:688)
  - Ren d'Harnoncourt, 1961, 1968-1970; Briggs, Mrs., William Harlowe (ALS) Graff, Mrs., Robert Daniel (incl. ALS) Lowry, Bates Mahlow, Dietrich (Stadt Nurnberg) Parkinson, Elizabeth B. Rockefeller, David File incl. clippings, copy of d'Hoodles, MoMA Members Newsletter 1968 October, d' Harnoncourt memorial tribute brochure 1968 October 8, New York Times article "Ren d'Harnoncourt" 1968 August 25 by William S. Lieberman, d'Harnoncourt memo re: Future building program (Box 1, Folder 1.465 mf 2194:807)
  - Huntington Hartford, 1950, 1952, 1955-1960, 1963-1965; Chamberlain, Betty (Art News; incl. ALS) Colin, Ralph F. (Roseman Goldmark Colin & Kaye) Devree, Howard (The New York Times) Gaszynski, Michael (Huntington Hartford Foundation; incl. TLS) Goldstone, Harmon H. (The Municipal Art Society) Holska, Walter J. (Winthrop, Stimson, Putnam and Roberts) Husted, James W. (Winthrop, Stimson, Putman and Roberts) Lindon, Mrs., Jacques McAndrew, John (Farnsworth Art Museum, Wellesley College) Mocsanyi, Paul (United Press Associations; incl. TLS, article) Weinhardt, Jr., Carl J. (Huntington Hartford Gallery of Modern Art) File incl. clippings, news release summary of The Proposed Huntington Hartford Pavilion at the Southeast Corner of Central Park, summary of press comments - MoMA vs. Hartford as of 1959 February 9, AHB ALS 1956 June 15, remarks of Rep. Frank Thompson, Jr. to the Ballet Theater 1955, December 8 (Box 1, Folder 1.466 mf 2194:913)
  - Heller Catalogue, 1961-1963; Heller, Ben Rasmussen, Waldo (TLS) Seitz, William C. (incl. Draft of Heller article with AHB corrections) File incl. preface to Ben Heller Collection catalogue (Box 1, Folder 1.467 mf 2195:6)
  - Hirshhorn Museum, 1974; File incl. TL MSB-Hirshhorn re: refusal of invitation for dinner for opening of Museum (Box 1, Folder 1.468 mf 2195:43)
  - I, 1960-1961, 1966, 1968-1969, 1974; ICOM (work sessions of Modern Art Committee - ICOM conference 1974 April 8-12, list of committee members and invited participants of conference) Iddings, Curtis Ingersoll, R. Sturgis (incl TLS) International Congress of Art Historians (Biebel, Franklin M.; Chastal, Andr;La Revue de l'Art; Meiss, Millard; Princeton University; incl. background information on the twentieth International Congress of the History of Art 1961 September (Box 1, Folder 1.469 mf 2195:46)
  - A. I. C. A. [International Association of Art Critics], Hamilton, George Heard (Sterling and Francine Clark Art Institute) Lassaigne, Jacques Sandler, Irving Spiteris, Tony File incl. list of members 1965, 1960, program for 20th general assembly of the A. I. C. A. 1968 September 8-15, agenda for the 18th general assembly 1966, September 26-28 (Box 1, Folder 1.470 mf 2195:85)
  - I. I. C. A. [International Institute of Contemporary Arts], 1955-1956, 1958-1959; Drew, Jane B. Goeller, Mrs., Vera B. Hodes, Barnet (Arvey, Hodes and Mantynband) Lawson, Julie (TLS) Penrose, Roland (incl. 3 ALS, 2 TLS) (Box 1, Folder 1.471 mf 2195:184)
  - I. C. A. [Institute of Contemporary Arts], 1937-1938, 1947-1951, 1953-1957, 1959, 1961, 1966; Alloway, Lawrence Clark, Stephen, C. Cooper, Douglas (corresp. re.) Davies, Thomas (incl. ALS) Davis, Elmer Dolan, Patrick (Patrick Dolan and Associates Ltd.; incl. TLS) Frankfurter, Alfred (Art News) Gregory, Eric C. (Perry Lund Humphries & Co. Ltd.; incl. 3 TLS) Grohmann, Will (TLS) Hodes, Barnet (incl. TLS) Kloman, A. J. T. Lewisohn, Sam A. Mesens, E. L. T. (The London Gallery, Ltd.) Penrose, Roland (incl. 3 ALS, 6 TLS) Read, Herbert (incl. TLS) Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller III, Mrs., John D. Sommerville, Lilian Spivack, S. S. Woods, S. John File incl. press release with AHB notes, copy of Carlton House Terrace Project: A Center for the Arts and Design 1966 January, The Institute of Contemporary Arts' Appeal, American Culture and the I. C. A. record of activities 1950-1956, A statement of the policy and aims of the Institute by the members of the Organizing Committee (Box 1, Folder 1.472 mf 2195:218)
  - Invitations - General, 1963-; Asia Society (Young, Jr., Kenneth T.) Alumni Federation of Columbia University, Inc. (Walsh, Lawrence E. TL re: Alumni Fall Reunion) American Association of Museums (Parkhurst, Charles) American Bank & Trust Company (opening of Bank 14th art exhibit 1971 April 6) Art Gallery of Toronto (Morrow, Graham; A Tribute to Samuel J. Sachs 1971 May 20) Art Students League of New York (Everett, Walker G.) Art Quarterly, The(Gettier, Astrid E.; invitation re: the annual meeting of the consultative committee) Boston Museum of Fine Arts (Centennial 1970 February 4) Brooklyn Museum, The (Buechner, Thomas S.) Brown University (Licht, Fred) Boys' Latin School Fathers' Club (Regan, Ronald K.) California at Berkeley, University of (Freudenheim, Tom L.; Heyns, Roger W.) Carnegie Institute (von Groschwitz, Gustave) Chicago, The University of (Brauer, Jerald C.) City Art Museum of Saint Louis (Buckley, Charles E.; invitation re: works of art of the 19th and 20th centuries collected by Louis and Joseph Pulitzer, Jr.) Cleveland Museum of Art, The Columbia University (Pagnano, Joseph; Krik, Grayson) Connecticut, The University of (Babbidge, Homer D., Jr.) Corcoran Gallery of Art, The (Williams, Jr., Hermann Warner) Conference on the Status of Soviet Jews (Thomas, Norman; incl. An Appeal of Conscience for the Jews of the Soviet Union) Cowles Communications Incorporated (Cowles, Gardner) Cunningham, Charles C. M/M Currier Gallery of Art, The (Woodbury, Peter) Des Moines Art Center (Tibbs, Thomas S.) Detroit Institute of Arts, The (Woods, Willis F.) Flint Institute of Arts (Hodge, G. Stuart) Griffin Gallery, The (Hooton, Bruce Dugg) Grinnell College (Leggett, Glenn) Grossman, Mrs., Donald (invitation re: The Hebrew Arts School for Music and Dance) Hellman, Daphne Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes (Gorostiza, Celestino) Inter-American Foundation for the Arts, The (Rubin, Jerome S.) International Art Exhibition of Japan (Abo, Hisatake;The Mainichi Newspapers) International Council of Museums Committee for Film and Television (Pirlot, C.) Javits, Marion (invitation re: preview of an experimental work by Robert Rauschenberg) Jette, Edith K. London Grafica Arts Incorporated (Caulkins, Bliss) Los Angeles County Museum of Art (opening of Art and Technology 1971 May 10; Carter, Edward W.; Tuchman, Maurice) Memorial Art Gallery, The (Prior, Harris K. ) Metropolitan Museum of Art, The Middlebury College (Armstrong James I.) Museum of Contemporary Art (van der Marck, Jan) Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Rathbone, Perry T.) Museum of Modern Art (special preview of Archipenko: The Parisian Years exhibition 1970 July 21) National Gallery of Canada (Boggs, Jean Sutherland) National Gallery of Victoria (Westbrook, Eric) National Museums of Canada, The (Ostiguy, J. P. W. TL re: Jacob Jordaens exhibition) New York Infirmary (Kress, Mrs., Rush H.) New York University (Arms, Jr., Richard G.) Philadelphia Museum of Art (Marceau, Henri) Phoenix Art Museum (Hinkhouse, F. H.) Poetry Center Rhode Island School of Design (Irving, Mrs., Washington; Robbins, Daniel) Robert Lee Blaffer Trust (Owen, Mrs., Kenneth Dale) Rubn Darío Celebration (Lacayo, Mauricio Pallais; Sanson-Teran, Jose) Shih, Mrs., Hsio Wen Terry Dintenfass, Inc. Tremaine, Mrs., Burton University Roundtable (Wechter, Vivienne Thaul) Waddell, Richard Wright, M/M Paul Zeisler, Richard S. (Box 1, Folder 1.473 mf 2195:364)